snesclassics.com 2009-06-18

# SNES ROMs, Games & ROM Emulators Nintendo ROMs – free SNES ROMs From Super Nintendo Classics

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us on www.SNESClassics.com and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Web site and our products and services.

What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration/Purchase Information

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register to be a member of SNESClassics, register for certain services, register for email newsletters and alerts, or purchase items through our site. This data collection can include such personally identifiable information as name, company name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information (credit card information would ONLY be collected from our ebay and amazon affiliates). You may also provide additional comments on how you see SNESClassics servicing your needs and interests.

Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs ("Log Files") to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them. Personally identifiable information is not stored in these cookies, web beacons, or clear gifs. We use a third-party tracking service, that uses cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, usage and volume statistic to help us better understand the needs of our visitors.

How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You have the opportunity to opt in, or opt out of these specific types of communications in our member center. You have the opportunity to opt-out any time you receive an email from us by using the link provided at the bottom of the email communication. You also may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by contacting us.

Communications from our Site/Choice-Opt Out

If you register on our site or purchase any products from the site you can expect to receive a welcome email and/or an order confirmation email. If you have registered with our site, you will receive any of the communications (newsletters, updates, product information, alerts) that you have opted-in to receive. From time to time we may need to send critical service updates from the site. You may not opt-out of receiving these critical service updates. At any time you wish to change your preferences for receiving communications from the site, please visit our member center to change your preferences or by contacting us.

Blogs

If you use our blogs you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there, name/Web site, can be read, collected, or used by other users in this forum. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in the blogs. Violation of our Terms of Use Agreement can result in removal of your post or termination of membership.

What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See "Third Party Advertisers."

How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.   
Sharing Information with Third Parties

We enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who will be given access to personal information (including, but not limited to, your email address) for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you and that you have opted-in to receive, unless you opt out of receiving such communications in our membership center.

Service Providers

We use third parties to perform our credit card processing and email services on our site. (credit card information would ONLY be collected from our ebay and amazon affiliates). When you purchase a product from us, our affilates (Ebay, Amazon) credit card processing company will facilitate the transaction. An email service provider will provide our email services. We will share billing and email information as necessary to the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, including their own marketing purposes.

Business Transitions

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by various ad affiliates, our advertising partners. We share aggregate Web site usage information about users with potential advertisers for the purpose of targeting our Internet advertisements on this site.

These ad affiliates uses cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that these ad affiliates collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable.

Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You have the opportunity to opt-in for these notifications at registration, and you have the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers at a later date by contacting us.

How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us .

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

You can update your registration information online on our member center page. You may also request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by contacting us.

Certain Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties (as defined in our Terms of Use Agreement); (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; or (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those privacy rules and policies before proceeding.

Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to our privacy policies or procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

SNESClassics.com
